{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "ja",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "a",
      "answer": "ぁ"
    },
    {
      "question": "e",
      "answer": "え"
    },
    {
      "question": "ka",
      "answer": "か"
    },
    {
      "question": "i",
      "answer": "い"
    },
    {
      "question": "u",
      "answer": "う"
    },
    {
      "question": "o",
      "answer": "お"
    },
    {
      "question": "ku",
      "answer": "く"
    },
    {
      "question": "ke",
      "answer": "け"
    },
    {
      "question": "ko",
      "answer": "こ"
    },
    {
      "question": "sa",
      "answer": "さ"
    },
    {
      "question": "shi",
      "answer": "し"
    },
    {
      "question": "su",
      "answer": "す"
    },
    {
      "question": "se",
      "answer": "せ"
    },
    {
      "question": "so",
      "answer": "そ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ta",
      "answer": "た"
    },
    {
      "question": "chi",
      "answer": "ち"
    },
    {
      "question": "tsu",
      "answer": "つ"
    },
    {
      "question": "te",
      "answer": "て"
    },
    {
      "question": "to",
      "answer": "と"
    },
    {
      "question": "na",
      "answer": "な"
    },
    {
      "question": "ni",
      "answer": "に"
    },
    {
      "question": "nu",
      "answer": "ぬ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ne",
      "answer": "ね"
    },
    {
      "question": "no",
      "answer": "の"
    },
    {
      "question": "ha",
      "answer": "は"
    },
    {
      "question": "hi",
      "answer": "ひ"
    },
    {
      "question": "fu",
      "answer": "ふ"
    },
    {
      "question": "he",
      "answer": "へ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ho",
      "answer": "ほ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ma",
      "answer": "ま"
    },
    {
      "question": "mi",
      "answer": "み"
    },
    {
      "question": "mu",
      "answer": "む"
    },
    {
      "question": "me",
      "answer": "め"
    },
    {
      "question": "mo",
      "answer": "も"
    },
    {
      "question": "ya",
      "answer": "や"
    },
    {
      "question": "yu",
      "answer": "ゆ"
    },
    {
      "question": "yo",
      "answer": "よ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ra",
      "answer": "ら"
    },
    {
      "question": "ri",
      "answer": "り"
    },
    {
      "question": "ru",
      "answer": "る"
    },
    {
      "question": "re",
      "answer": "れ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ro",
      "answer": "ろ"
    },
    {
      "question": "wa",
      "answer": "わ"
    },
    {
      "question": "wo",
      "answer": "を"
    },
    {
      "question": "n",
      "answer": "ん"
    },
    {
      "question": "ki",
      "answer": "き"
    }
  ]
}
